- 그래 - 알았어
레이첼, 동그란 원 안에 마시멜로 좀 넣을래?
아니, 동그란 원 안에 마시멜로 넣는 건 네가 해
난 이거나 할래
매번 이렇다니까
나도 잠깐 엉덩이 붙이고 앉아서 풋볼이나 봐야겠다
전반 끝났다
우리, 시합 안 할래? 편 갈라서 한 판 하자
재밌겠다
나도 해도 돼? 풋볼 한번도 안해 봤는데
그럼, 챈들러 커버해
아니, 난 하기 싫어
하자, 너 재니스랑 헤어지고 아무 의욕도 없잖아
그런 소리 마
욕실 가운 입고, 종일 땅콩 버터 먹고 싶고
아침부터 술독에 빠지고 싶어 나도 목표가 있는 놈이야
챈들러, 이제 그만 잊어버려
시합하면서 시원한 바람을 쐬면 재니스도 잊혀질 거야
너 시합 안 하면 숫자가 안 맞으니까 다들 화낼 거야
- 하자 - 알았어, 할게
야호!
- 하자, 로스 - 뭐?
풋볼하자
모니카랑 난 풋볼하면 안돼
누가 그래, 너희 엄마?
그래
추수감사절 때마다 우린 풋볼 시합을 했어
일명 '겔러볼'이라고 했지
설마, 그게 자랑은 아니겠지?
로스 오빠랑 난 주장이었어
서로 이기려고 눈이 멀었는데 어느 해인가...
내가 실수로 오빠 코를 부러뜨렸어
그건 실수가 아니었어
내가 따라붙으니까 피둥피둥한 팔로 내 얼굴을 갈기고
냅다 도망쳤어
어쨌든 우리가 터치다운했어
시합에 이기지도 못했잖아
터치다운은 기록되지도 않았어 불법 행위에 야만 행위였거든
코를 부러뜨린 거 말야
내가 이겼어
그럼 왜 '겔러컵'을 못 받았지?
'겔러컵'도 있었어?
그래, 시합에서 이기면 받는 트로피였어
아빠가 무승부라고 하셨지 우리 싸우는 거에 신물이 나셨거든
그래서 트로피를 가져가서...
호수에 던져버리셨어
그래서 저주가 시작된 거야?
어쨌든...
엄마가 그때부터 다시는 풋볼 못하게 하셨어
괜찮아 이제 시합해도 될 거야
벌써 12년이나 지났잖아
잠깐 좀 볼까?
뭐?
좋아, 하자
잠깐, 공원에 어떻게 가지? 엄마가 길 건너지 말랬는데
피비, 받아
좋아, 시작하자
나한테 던져, 나한테!
간다
얼굴 맞을 뻔했어
좋아, 우리 주장 고르자
꼬붕들도
어떻게 하는 건데?
- 찍기 하자 - 뭐?
- 찍자구 - 찍는 거야
로스 오빠랑 내가 주장이야
- 나부터 찍을게, 먼저 고를 거야 - 좋아
- 조이 - 고마워
모니카, 난 네 친구야
자기도 뽑힐 테니까 기다려봐 챈들러
- 로스? - 피비
봐, 자기 고르잖아
고른 게 아니라 나만 남은 거잖아
좋아, 그럼 쓰레기통에서 가로등까지 하는 거다
우리가 시작할게
좋아, 잘 들어 정확히 28분 후에
부저가 울리는 거다
꼭 프로 같은데
좋아, 작전 타임 이리 와
잠깐, 기다려
신난다 작전 타임은 처음이야
- 좋아 - 챈들러를 어떻게 생각하니?
- 피비, 뭐하는 건지 알아? - 그럼
조이가 공을 잡으면 너랑 내가 블로킹하는 거야
블로킹이 뭐야?
뭐하는지 안다고 했잖아
시합 얘긴 줄 몰랐지
해산
이 공은 재니스다 이 공은 재니스다
이 나쁜... 조심해
미안, 미안해 그냥 손으로 던진다
- 내가 받을게 - 뛰어!
7대 빵입니다!
괜찮아?
그래, 가자
패자가 걸어가네
패자가 말을 하네
그만해, 패자가 까부네
43, 74...
- 그냥 할래? - 그래
- 간다! - 원 미시시피, 투 미시시피, 쓰리!
여기야, 여기
받을 뻔했어
- 7대 7 될 뻔했어 - 그래
이번엔 쭉 내려가서 오른쪽으로 가는 거다
- 알았어 - 해산!
잠깐, 난 어떡해?
넌... 그냥 돌아
얼마 동안?
눈앞이 노래질 때까지
- 알았어 - 해산
준비, 간다!
원 미시시피, 투 미시시피 받아, 받아!
안돼, 안돼!
공 잡아줘서 고마워요
- 미식 축구하는 거예요? - 네
외국에서 오셨나봐요
네덜란드예요
안녕, 난 조이예요
난 마하예요
미안해요, 네덜란드 뒷말은 못 알아듣겠어요
조이, 풋볼하다 말고 뭐해? 안녕, 난 챈들러예요
안녕, 챈들러
이름이 네덜란드인데 마한이라고도 한대
- 마하예요 - 마카
- 마하 - 마하아안
뭐해? 계속해야지 두 번째 다운이야
세 번째야
웃기지 마, 두 번째야
- 와우 - 뭐가 와우야?
잘났다고 박박 우기는 거 보니까 놀랍기만 하다
우겼다고? 두 번째 맞잖아
그래, 두 번째라고 해
불쌍해서 봐준다
다 들었어
들으라고 한 소리야
여기서 구경해도 돼요?
- 그럼요, 앉아서 봐요 - 어서 앉아요
- 잘됐다 - 그럼
전화번호 물어보면 어떨까?
고맙지만 내가 직접 해야 점수가 올라갈 거야
그게 아니라 날 위해서 물어봐 달라고...
재니스를 잊으라고 했잖아
그야 그렇지
- 네 생각이 그렇다면 양보할게 - 고마워
뭐? 양보한다고?
나 혼자 나서봤자 어림없다는 소리야 뭐야?
큰 소리 내고 싶진 않지만
그래!
괜찮아, 넌 여자엔 약하지만 숫자에는 강하잖아
숫자? 숫자로 밀어부치려고?
좋아, 관두자
양보하지 마 누가 이기나 붙어보자구
챈들러, 왼쪽으로 무작정 달리는 거야, 알았지?
- 그리고 자기? - 알아, 계속 돌라고?
난 작전 타임이나 하고 왔다갔다만 하는 것 같아
그럼 나가서 구경할래?
- 잠깐 좀 볼까? - 그래
좋아
- 좋아, 간다 - 간다!
원 미시시피, 투 미시시피, 쓰리 미시시피
놓쳤잖아
뭐하는 거야? 내가 제일 좋아하는 옷인데
두 개로 갈라줬잖아
나 계산 잘하지?
좋아, 양보하려고 했는데
없었던 걸로 하고 자존심 상할 각오나 하셔
그래, 평생 각오하면서 살고 있다
지금 네 얘길 하는 거야!
좋아, 간다
동점이야, 시간 없어
42, 38, 간다!
내가 받을게
팔 부러졌나봐
- 피비, 달려 - 피비, 뛰어
- 터치다운이야 - 터치다운!
아니, 부저가 울렸어 이건 점수에 포함 안 돼
- 부저는 나중에 울렸어 - 전에 울렸어
- 나중에 - 전에
- 그게 문제가 돼? - 그럼!
터치다운했어, 최초의 터치다운이야, 그러니까...
피비, 그건 알지만 점수는 안돼
- 왜 안된다는 거야? - 사기꾼이 우기기까지 하네
세상에
좋아, 오빠는 유치하게 굴어 난 오빠랑 달라
그래
다리나 부러져라
좋아, 속임수를 써서 이기겠다? 맘대로 해
피비, 터치다운했다고 쳐 네가 이겼어
- 신난다! - 아니
또 오빠 술수에 넘어갈 줄 알아?
코뼈가 부러졌다고, 귀가 짝짝이라 부저가 빨랐다고 핑계 대지마
동점이라고 하고 후반에 다시 하자구
난 사기꾼하고 시합 안 해
하고 싶어도 다리 부러져서 못해!
시합 안하곤 못 배길걸
왜 못 배겨?
이기면 이걸 가져가니까
'겔러컵'이잖아
사자 머리 인형 너희도 봤니?
응
그렇군
어디서 났어?
엄마 아빠가 오빠 병원에 데려갔을 때
내가 호수에 헤엄쳐 들어가 꺼냈지
내 컵이야
아니, 갖고 싶으면 시합에서 이기면 되잖아
좋아, 근데 저녁은 언제 먹어?
피비, 이리 와 시합해야지, 작전 타임
조이, 시합에 집중해
그게 말처럼 쉬워? 챈들러가 여자 가까이 있잖아
좋아, 챈들러만 해결하면 시합에 집중할 수 있겠어?
어떻게 하려고?
공이나 받게 해
- 나머지는 내가 할게 - 알았어
- 가자 - 좋아
조심해!
여자한테 태클 당했대요
이런 구경하기 힘들답니다
왜 태클을 걸고 난리야?
왜? 건드리기만 했는데 넘어진 거야
거칠게 하겠다 이거지? 좋았어
너무 재밌다
어디서 난 거야?
한참 놀았더니 배고파서...
42대 21 상대가 안돼, 우리가 이겼지롱
네가 이긴 것도 당연하지 너부터 팀을 골랐으니까
우기지 마
그냥 받아들이면 되잖아 내가 오빠보다 낫다는 증거야
할 말 없으니까 코웃음으로 무마하시겠다?
좋아, 내가 증명해 보일까?
조이랑 레이첼을 바꿔도 우리 팀이 이길 수 있어
뭐? 남자 대 여자라구?
말도 안되는 소리하지 마 내가 터치다운 세 번은 한다
그럼 해봐
여자들한테 질까봐 무서워서 못하는 거 아냐?
좋아, 레이첼, 모니카 편 해 조이, 넌 우리 편이야
날 바꾸는 거야?
이리 와, 레이첼 이기는 팀에 들어오면 좋잖아
나 게임해도 돼?
좋아!
게임 끝났어요? 식사하는 거예요?
아뇨, 아직이요 팀을 바꾸는 거예요
같은 팀에서 뛰면 챈들러가 나 때문에 실력발휘 못할걸요
좋아, 그럼 시작하자
잠깐만, 조이
네덜란드 사람들이 어디서 왔게?
펜실배니아 네덜란드는 펜실배니아에서 왔지
다른 사람은? 네덜란드 근처에서 왔을까?
웃겼어
네덜란드는 피터팬이랑 팅커벨이 사는 동화 속 나라야
맙소사
지리 공부는 나중에 하고 시합이나 하자구
- 아니, 나 얘하고 시합 못해 - 나도 마찬가지야
좋아, 더는 못 봐줘 솔직히 말해봐요
둘 중에 누가 더 좋아요?
지금 뭐하는 거야?
둘 중에요?
데이트하자고 한다면요 풍차 나라에 누굴 데려갈래요?
지금 그걸 골라야 한다면 좀 이상하긴 하지만...
- 챈들러로 하죠 - 좋았어!
잠깐, 질문을 이해 못한 거 같은데
그럼 후크 선장이 직접 설명해주시지
미안해요, 조이 제 진심이에요
들었지? 진심이라잖아 양보맨 씨!
내가 이기고 네가 졌어 다같이 축하의 박수를!
우후!
다시 생각해보니까 아무도 안 고르는 게 좋겠어요
뭐라구요?
이제 보니까 당신 너무 얄팍하고 가벼워요, 안녕
안됐다, 앞으로도 여자랑 잠자리 할 일은 없겠구나
그게 중요한 게 아냐 중요한 건 날 골랐단 거지
이제부터 난 데이트할 때 넌 "준비, 땡"이나 하면서 놀라구
싸움은 나중에 하자 이럴 시간이 없어
우리가 지고 있어 여자들한테 지고 있다구
여자들한테 왜 져?
42대 21이야
말도 안돼 아까 내가 다 이겨 놨는데
시합하는 거야 마는 거야? 털복숭이 친구들!
꼭 이겨야 돼 세상 모든 여자들을 위해서야
지금까지 만났던 재수없는 데이트 상대들을 생각해봐
사랑을 나누면서도 한쪽 눈으론 TV 보느라 정신없는 남자들을!
너도 한쪽 안경 쓴 사람이랑 데이트해봤어?
세상 모든 여자들을 위한 시합이야
- 쓸어버리자구 - 그래, 쓸어버리자!
좋아, 솔직히 나도 쓸어버리고 싶지만 쟤들은 남자야
어떻게 남자 셋을 이겨?
아직 1분 30초 남았으니까 2점은 딸 수 있어
2점이면 돼
피비, 후크 다시 풀어
레이첼, 넌 계속 돌아
싫어, 나도 시켜줘 아무도 날 커버 안한단 말야
그럴 만한 이유가 있어
무시하지 마 나도 뭐든 할 수 있어
공 던질게, 던지게 해줘 나도 선수잖아
그래, 던지게 해줘
좋아, 뒤에서 어슬렁거리다 공 받아서 피비한테 던져
- 그래 - 좋아
해산, 해산
좋아, 32, 71, 간다!
미안, 괜찮아?
안 괜찮아!
미안해, 한꺼번에 달려드니까 어떻게 할지 모르겠더라구
30초 남았다
좋아, 그럼 사자 머리 인형 우리 거야?
빨리, 시간 없단 말야
- 작전 타임! - 좋아
이번이 마지막이네
피비, 공 받을 준비하고 레이첼, 넌 계속 돌아
알았어
해산
내가 해냈다, 터치다운! 우리가 이겼어
야호!
레이첼, 안됐지만...
엔드 존은 저 기둥부터야 5피트 모자라, 그러니까...
우리가 이긴 거야
잠깐, 어떻게 되는 거야?
아직 아웃 된 거 아니니까 시합 안 끝났잖아
- 이거 놔, 놓으란 말야 - 안돼, 네가 놔
- 이리 내놔! - 난 연약한 여자라구
그만하자, 추수감사절인데 이기고 지는 게 무슨 상관이야
중요한 건 네덜란드 아가씨가 날 골랐다는 거야
네덜란드는 챈들러를 사랑해! 감사합니다, 아름다운 밤이에요!
우리 풋볼 자주 하자
리그 같은 것도 있잖아
내셔널 풋볼 리그가 있지 않던가?
그래, 있지 일요일, 월요일 밤에 시합해
아쉽다 월요일 밤에 일 나가는데
정말 맛있다
애들 불러와야 되지 않아?
배고프면 들어오겠지
놔
- 네가 놔 - 싫어
왜 항상 우리만 공 붙들고 나동그러져 있지?
몰라, 다른 사람들은 관심이 없나봐
눈 온다
- 이거 놔 - 제발 좀 놔
Oh, come on!
It's your Thanksgiving too. Instead of watching football, you could help.
We know.
You wanna put the marshmallows in concentric circles.
No, you want to put them in concentric circles.
I want to do this.
Every year.
The One With the Football
To the 10, to the 5. Touchdown, Giants!
You know, for once, I am gonna try to watch one of these things.
Halftime.
Who wants to throw the ball around? Get a little 3-on-3 going?
-That would be fun! -Can I play too?
I've never played football, ever.
Great! You can cover Chandler.
I don't really want to play.
You never do anything since you and Janice broke up.
Not true.
I wanted to wear my bathrobe and eat peanut clusters all day.
And start drinking in the morning. Don't say I don't have goals!
You have to start getting over her, all right?
If you play, maybe it'll take your mind off Janice.
If you don't, everyone will be mad at you because the teams won't be even.
All right, I'll play.
Let's do it! Ross?
-What? -Wanna play football?
Monica and I aren't supposed to play football.
Says who? Your mom?
Every Thanksgiving, we used to have a touch football game...
...called The Geller Bowl.
No, no, no. You say that proudly!
Anyway, Ross and l were always captains.
It got kind of competitive, and one year, Geller Bowl Vl...
... I accidentally broke Ross' nose.
It was so not an accident.
She saw I was about to tag her, so she threw...
... her big fat grandma-arm elbow in my face...
...and just kept running.
To score the winning touchdown, by the way.
You did not win the game. The touchdown didn't count...
... because of the spectacularly illegal, and savage, nose-breaking.
I won the game.
Yeah? Then how come you didn't get the Geller Cup?
There was a Geller Cup?
Yes, the trophy you got if you won the game.
But Dad said nobody won, and he was sick of our fighting.
So he took the trophy...
...threw it in the lake.
And was the curse lifted?
Anyway...
... Mom said we weren't allowed to play football again.
You know what? I think we should play a game.
I mean, come on. It's been 12 years.
Can I see you for a second?
Wuss!
All right, we're gonna play.
Wait. How we gonna get there? My mom won't let me cross the street.
Here you go.
-Let's bring it in. -Wait.
Honey, throw it to me!
Here you go.
That almost hit me in the face!
We have to pick captains.
And then "Tenilles."
So how do we decide that?
-Why don't we just bunny up? -What?
-Bunny! -Bunny!
Looks like Ross and I are captains.
I bunnied first, so I get to pick first. Joey.
-Thank you. -Monica!
I'm your best friend.
Sweetie, don't worry, you'll get picked.
Sweetie, now I pick you.
You don't pick me. You're stuck with me!
Okay. So let's see.
Let's play from the trash can to the light post, right?
Two-hand touch. We'll kick off.
People, listen. I've got 28 minutes...
... before I have to baste again.
Wow, just like in the pros.
Okay, huddle up!
-Huddle up over here! -Wait for me! Wait for me!
Oh, cool! My first huddle.
So what do you guys really think of Chandler?
You know what you're doing, right?
Joey will catch it. We'll block.
What's "block"?
-I thought you knew what you were doing. -I thought you meant in life!
Break!
The ball is Janice. The ball is Janice.
Son of a!
-Come on! -I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You know what? We're just gonna throw it.
I got it!
Go, go, go!
Score! Seven to nothing!
Honey, you okay?
Come on, let's go.
Losers walk.
Yeah? Losers talk.
Actually, losers rhyme.
Forty-three...
...seventy-four....
You wanna go shotgun?
-One Mississippi, two Mississippi.... -Over here! Over here!
I almost caught it!
Great. Now the score's seven to almost seven.
On this play, I want you to do a down-and-out to the right, okay?
-Break! -Wait. What am I gonna do?
You?
You go long.
How long?
Until we start to look very small.
Break!
One Mississippi
Switch! Switch! Switch!
Thanks for stopping our ball.
You are playing American football?
Wow! You're, like, from a whole other country!
I'm Dutch.
Hi, I'm Joey.
I am Margha.
Sorry, Dutch, I didn't get that last little bit.
You wanna play football or Hi, I'm Chandler.
Hello, Chandler.
Her name is Dutch and also "Margham."
Come on, guys! Let's go! Second down!
-Hello? It's third down. -No, it's not. It's second.
Wow.
"Wow" what?
How it just amazes me that you're still pulling stuff like this.
-Pulling what? It's second down. -Okay, it's second down.
Take all the second downs you need.
-I heard that. -Well, I said it loud.
It is okay if I stay and watch?
-Just sit right there. -Yeah, why don't you stick around?
-That went well. -I think so.
I was thinking about asking her for her number.
Thanks, man, but it makes a stronger statement if I ask for it myself.
I was thinking about for me, as part of that getting-over-Janice thing.
Oh, yeah. That.
If it means that much, I'll let you have her.
Thanks.
"Let me have her"?
You mean if you didn't, I wouldn't have a shot?
I don't like to say it out loud...
... but yeah!
We all have our strengths. You're better with numbers and stuff.
Math? You're giving me math?
All right, you know what? Forget about it.
You go for the girl. We'll see who gets her.
I want you to run a post-pattern to the left. And, sweetie
Yeah, I know. Go long.
All I'm doing is running back and forth from the huddle.
Well, you wanna just stay out there?
Can I see that for a second?
Okay, let's go.
-I got Chandler! -Hike!
One Mississippi, two Mississippi, three Mississippi.
Fumble!
What's the matter with you? This is my favorite jersey.
Well, now you have two.
Hey, I am good at math!
That's it. I was still gonna let you have her.
But now, prepare to feel bad about yourself.
I've been preparing for that my entire life!
Or something about you that's mean!
Come on, guys. Let's go.
Tie score. We're running out of time.
Forty-two, 38, hike!
I got it!
Broken boobs!
-Pheebs, run! -Run, Phoebe, run!
Touchdown! Touchdown!
The buzzer buzzed. It doesn't count.
-After the snap. -Before the snap.
-After. -Before.
-Does it really matter? -Yes!
But I made a touchdown. It was my first touchdown.
Pheebs, that's great. Doesn't count.
-Does so count. -Cheater, cheater, compulsive eater.
Oh, my God!
That's fine. Maybe you haven't grown up, but I have.
Dead leg!
Okay, fine. You want to win by cheating, go ahead.
The touchdown does count. You win.
I won't do this again. I wanna beat you when you can't blame it...
...on the broken nose or the buzzer or the fact that you might have mono.
Let's just call this tie score and it's halftime.
First, I don't play with cheaters.
Second of all, you know I had swollen glands!
You know what? I think you'll play.
Oh, really? Why's that?
Because the winner gets this.
The Geller Cup!
Is everybody else seeing a troll doll nailed to a two-by-four?
Okay, good.
Where the hell did you get that?
When you went to the hospital for your nose...
...I swam into the lake and fished it out.
That cup is mine!
No, it's not. You want it, you're gonna have to win it.
So are we not having dinner at all?
Come on, let's go. It's time to get serious. Huddle up.
IKeep your head in the game.
It's hard, you know? His huddle's close to the Dutch girl.
If I take Chandler out of the running, will you be able to focus?
-What are you gonna do? -Just make sure he catches the ball.
I'll do the rest.
-Come on, you wuss! -Okay, come on.
I got it!
Come on! This way! Come on!
Look out!
Tackled by a girl! Bet you don't see that every day.
What's with the tackling?
What?
I just touched him and he went over.
Okay. You wanna play rough? We can play rough.
Let's get ready to rumble!
-Go, go, go! -Get her! Get her!
I love this game!
Where'd you get that?
I went really long.
Forty-two to 21.
Like the turkey, Ross is done!
You got to pick first, so you got the better team.
Pathetic! Why can't you just accept that we're winning...
... because I'm better than you?
Oh, what a great argument. Exhaling!
All right, I'll prove it to you.
I'll trade you Joey for Rachel and I'll still win the game.
What? The guys against the girls?
That's ridiculous because I'm only down by three touchdowns.
Then bring it on!
Unless you're afraid you might lose to a bunch of girls.
Fine. Rachel, you're with Monica. Joey, you're with me.
I can't believe you're trading me.
Let's see what it's like to be on a winning team for a change.
You're gonna let me play?
All right, then!
The game is over? We eat now?
The game's not over. We're switching teams.
Chandler finds me so intimidating that it's better if we're on the same team.
Okay, let's play. Let's go.
Hold on a second.
Where do Dutch people come from?
Well, the Pennsylvania Dutch come from Pennsylvania.
And the other Dutch people?
They come from somewhere near the Netherlands, right?
Nice try.
The Netherlands is this make-believe place...
...where Peter Pan and Tinker Bell live.
Oh, my.
Enough "geography for the insane." Let's play ball.
I'm not playing with this guy.
-Fine with me. -I've had enough of this.
Let's just cut to the chase. Heidi, which of my boys do you like?
What are you doing?
Which do I like?
Yeah, for dating, general merriment, taking back to your windmill?
Well, if I had to choose right now...
...which, by the way, I find really weird...
... I would have to say Chandler.
Wait a minute. She didn't understand the question.
Why don't you have Captain Hook explain it to her?
I'm sorry. That is my truth.
You hear that? That is her truth, Mr. "I'll Let You Have Her"!
I win! You suck! I rule all!
Mini-wave in celebration of me!
I am now thinking I would like to change my answer to "no one."
What?
I now find you shallow...
...and a dork.
Bye-bye.
Nice going.
You just saved yourself a couple months of sex.
It doesn't matter, because she picked me.
From now on, I get the dates...
...and you stay home on Saturday nights watching Ready, Set, Cook!
Save the breakthroughs for therapy. The clock is ticking.
We have no time and we are losing to girls.
We're not gonna lose to girls.
It's 42-21!
This sucks! I was just up by that much!
Are we playing football or what? Come on, you hairy-backed Marys!
We have to do this. We're playing for women everywhere.
Think about every lousy date you ever had.
Every guy who kept one eye on the TV while you were making out.
Oh, my God. You dated someone with a glass eye too?
Come on, okay? This is for all womankind. Let's kill them!
Yeah! IKill them!
All right, I want to kill them too.
But they're boys.
You know, how are we gonna beat three boys?
A minute and a half left and we're down by two points.
Two points, ladies.
Phoebe, you do a buttonhook again.
Rachel, you go long.
No, don't make me go long. Use me. They never cover me.
Honey, there's a reason.
I'm not lame, okay? I can do something.
Would you let me throw? This is my game too.
Let her throw the ball.
Sweep behind, I'll pitch it. You throw it downfield to Phoebe.
Thank you.
-Break! -Break!
All right, here we go.
Thirty-two, 71, hike!
One Mississippi, two Mississippi, three Mississippi!
Go, go, go!
Catch it!
-I'm so sorry. Are you okay? -No, I'm not okay!
They were coming at me and I didn't know what to do.
Thirty seconds left on the timer.
So we get to take that stupid troll thing home.
Come on! Hurry! We're running out of time.
Huddle up!
This is our last huddle!
All right, Phoebe, get open. Rachel...
...go long.
Okay.
Break!
I did it! Touchdown! We did it!
You know? Funny thing, actually. The end zone starts at that pole.
So you're five feet short. So...
...we win!
Yes, yes, yes!
Wait, explain something, though.
If nobody tagged Rachel, then isn't the play still going?
-Let me in, let me in! -No way! Let go!
Let go?! I'm a tiny little woman!
Come on, it's Thanksgiving!
It's not important who wins or loses.
The important thing is the Dutch girl picked me!
Me, not you! Holland loves Chandler! Thank you, Amsterdam! Good night!
We should play football more often.
Maybe there's a league we could join.
Isn't there a "national football league"?
Yes, there is. They play on Sundays and Monday nights.
Oh, shoot! I work Monday nights.
This stuffing is amazing. Do you think we should bring them some?
When they're hungry, they'll come in.
-Let go! -No, you let go!
How come it's always us left holding the ball?
I don't know. I guess the other people just don't care enough.
Hey, it's starting to snow.
-Give it to me! Let go! -Let it go! Come on, let go!